<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mybeer.recipes</title>
    <link>https://mybeer.recipes/</link>
    <description>Recent content on mybeer.recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mybeer.recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://mybeer.recipes/nondisclosureagreement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mybeer.recipes/nondisclosureagreement/</guid>
      <description>Non-disclosure Agreement
Confidentiality
The Tester will not disclose Software or any comments regarding Software to any third party without the prior written approval of mybeer.recipes. The Tester will maintain the confidentiality of Software with at least the same degree of care that you use to protect your own confidential and proprietary information, but not less than a reasonable degree of care under the circumstances. The Tester will not be liable for the disclosure of any confidential information which is:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://mybeer.recipes/privacypolicy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mybeer.recipes/privacypolicy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy
Ross Merrigan built the mybeer.recipes app as a Commercial app. This SERVICE is provided by Ross Merrigan and is intended for use as is.
This page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.
If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://mybeer.recipes/termsandconditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mybeer.recipes/termsandconditions/</guid>
      <description>Terms &amp;amp; Conditions
By downloading or using the app, these terms will automatically apply to you – you should make sure therefore that you read them carefully before using the app. You’re not allowed to copy, or modify the app, any part of the app, or our trademarks in any way. You’re not allowed to attempt to extract the source code of the app, and you also shouldn’t try to translate the app into other languages, or make derivative versions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>